http://www.cme-meetings.com/about-aei/privacy-policy/

CME Continuing Medical Legal Dental Education - AEI Seminars – Accredited CME, CLE & CE Weekly in Beautiful Places. Since 1982.
Sun & Ski Destinations
DestinationsSun DestinationsARIZONAScottsdaleCALIFORNIALake TahoePalm SpringsCANADAWhistler, B.C.CARIBBEANArubaBahamas, Paradise IslandGrand CaymanCOLORADOAspenSteamboat SpringsVailFLORIDABoca Raton/Boynton BeachIslamorada, KeysNaples/Bonita BeachOrlandoSandestinSanibel IslandSouth Beach MiamiHAWAIIHonoluluLahaina (Maui)Wailea (Maui)MEXICOCancunNEVADALas VegasSOUTH CAROLINAHilton Head IslandKiawah IslandMyrtle BeachUTAHPark City (near Deer Valley/Canyons)WYOMINGJackson HoleSki DestinationsCALIFORNIALake TahoeCANADAWhistler, B.C.COLORADOAspenBeaver CreekBreckenridgeKeystoneSnowmassSteamboat SpringsTellurideVailMONTANABig SkyUTAHPark City (near Deer Valley/Canyons)WYOMINGJackson Hole
Tuition
Schedule
Discounted Ski Passes,
Equipment and moreReceive $100 CASH
Discounted Ski Passes and Equipment Rentals
Discounted Lodging
Repeat Course for Free
About AEI &
Contact UsAbout AEI
Contact Us
Testimonials
The 2020-2021 Medical-Dental-Legal Update
Your privacy is important to American Educational Institute (AEI).
This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that AEI collects, and the ways in which AEI uses that personal information.
Credit
This document was created using a Contractology template available at www.contractology.com.
Personal information collection
AEI may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:
information about your use of this website;
information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the
website;
information about transactions carried out over this website;
information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website
services;
any other information that you send to AEI.
Using personal information
AEI may use your personal information to:
administer this website;
personalize the website for you;
enable your access to and use of the website services;
send to you products that you purchase;
supply to you services that you purchase;
send to you statements and invoices;
collect payments from you; and
send you marketing communicati­ons.
Where AEI discloses your personal information to its agents or
sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will
be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of
this privacy statement.
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes
identified elsewhere above, AEI may disclose your personal information to the
extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal
proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish,
exercise or defend its legal rights.
This site is being monitored by one or more third-party monitoring
software(s) and may use pixels which capture information [which may identify the
device used to visit this site] which helps us assess and attempt to satisfy
your needs as a customer or potential customer. You may control the data being
collected from your visit by clicking on http://www.whosclicking.com/pages/optout.aspx
Securing your data
AEI will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent
the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
AEI will store all the personal information you provide [on its secure
servers].
Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website
will be protected by encryption technology.
Cross-border data transfers
Information that AEI collects may be stored and processed in and transferred
between any of the countries in which AEI operates to enable the use of the
information in accordance with this privacy policy.
You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.
Updating this statement
AEI may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this
website.
You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any
changes.
Other websites
This website contains links to other websites.
AEI is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any
third party.
Contact AEI
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or AEI’s treat­ment
of your personal information, please write:
by email to Info@AEIseminars.com;
or
by post to 401 South Old Woodward, Suite 333 . Birmingham, MI
. 48009.
The Medical-Dental-Legal UpdateProgram Description
Course Objectives
Accreditation
Program Faculty
Free Repeat
Sun & Ski Destinations
DestinationsSun DestinationsARIZONAScottsdaleCALIFORNIALake TahoePalm SpringsCANADAWhistler, B.C.CARIBBEANArubaBahamas, Paradise IslandGrand CaymanCOLORADOAspenSteamboat SpringsVailFLORIDABoca Raton/Boynton BeachIslamorada, KeysNaples/Bonita BeachOrlandoSandestinSanibel IslandSouth Beach MiamiHAWAIIHonoluluLahaina (Maui)Wailea (Maui)MEXICOCancunNEVADALas VegasSOUTH CAROLINAHilton Head IslandKiawah IslandMyrtle BeachUTAHPark City (near Deer Valley/Canyons)WYOMINGJackson HoleSki DestinationsCALIFORNIALake TahoeCANADAWhistler, B.C.COLORADOAspenBeaver CreekBreckenridgeKeystoneSnowmassSteamboat SpringsTellurideVailMONTANABig SkyUTAHPark City (near Deer Valley/Canyons)WYOMINGJackson Hole
Tuition
Schedule
Discounted Ski Passes,
Equipment and moreReceive $100 CASH
Discounted Ski Passes and Equipment Rentals
Discounted Lodging
Repeat Course for Free
About AEI &
Contact UsAbout AEI
Contact Us
Testimonials
Facebook
CME Continuing Medical Legal Dental Education - AEI Seminars. © 2015 American Educational Institute. All rights reserved. Website design & development © vlado.cz.
AEI provides continuing medical, dental, and legal education conferences at vacation destinations. Our CME, CDE, and CLE programs are fully accredited.
Request a Full Course Catalog No, thanks
Standard Tuition
$645
Discounted Tuition
Medical Resident
$545
RN, RNP, RDH or PA
$545
Active duty military personnel, please call for additional discount.
